Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 10: Pins and Ribbons, 1895-2000; 8 boxes
  - Class of 1871 Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 41)
    Bronze with a tiger head; a orange and black ribbon with stars in black; a metal piece "71" hanging from the mouth of the tiger.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 42)
    Orange (faded) and black; round with "1984" in white.
  - Class of 1886 ribbon, 1 item (Box 190)
    Orange with "Class '86" in black.
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 194)
    Orange and Black.
  - Ivy Club Pin, circa 1888; 1 item (Box 12)
    Ivy Club Pin 1888.
    EX4791
  - Class of 1879 lapel button, circa 1879; 1 item (Box 12)
    Lapel button. Class of 1879.
    EX4563
  - Buttons, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Silver with "'16."
  - Buttons, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Buttons or badges. Black with "'16" in silver (2)
  - Class of 1923 40th reunion pin, 1963; 1 item (Box 5)
    White and round with "My Hat!!"and "'23's 40th" in orange and "Augie Weishaar."
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 5)
    Orange and black and round with "Princeton" in black on white background.
  - Pin with football, undated; 1 item (Box 5)
    Orange and black and round with "Princeton"in reverse colors. Orange and black ribbons attached, with gold football hanging from chain.
  - Class of 1934 reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 5)
    Orange and round with "1934," seal, and "T.G.F.E." in black. "Frank Buchner."
  - Class of 1902 20th reunion pin, 1922; 1 item (Box 9)
    Orange and round with "'02 Twentieth Reunion" in black.
    AR.2000.017
  - 1923 reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 9)
    Orange and round with seal and "1923""Augie Weishaar."
  - 1934 reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 9)
    Orange and round with "Old '34" and drawing of Nassau Hall in black. "Frank Buchner."
  - "13" reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 15)
    Black and round with "13" in orange, orange rim.
  - Class of 1936 50th reunion pin, 1986; 1 item (Box 15)
    Orange and round with "50th Reunion 1936" in black. Name smeared. 1990 sticker.
  - "1901" pin, circa 1901; 1 item (Box 45)
    Pin "1901" Metal.
  - "88" pin, circa 1888; 1 item (Box 45)
    88 pin.
    EX4790
  - Cloister Inn pins, circa 1926; 1 item (Box 45)
    Cloister Inn pins. CWM initials.
    Anonymous gift in memory of Charles W Millard, Jr. '26.
  - Seal with anchors pin, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Pin, U. seal with anchors around it.
    AR.1993.011
  - "79" lapel pin, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Lapel pin. Groundbreaking shovel with "79."
  - "79" lapel pin, circa 1879; 1 item (Box 106)
    "79" black and orange.
  - "1935" lapel pin, undated; 1 item (Box 106)
    Black with shield and "1935."
  - "1935" lapel pin, undated; 1 item (Box 106)
    Gold with shield and "1935."
  - Lapel pin, undated; 1 item (Box 109)
    Covered in orange and black fabric.
    AR.2008.095
  - OSS pin, undated; 1 item (Box 116)
    OSS pin.
    Given to Luchet? '27 by Horton '42. Note attached.
  - Plastic Princeton Shield, undated; 1 item (Box 125)
    Hung from a "With One Accord" ribbon.
  - Metal pin "campus privilege", undated; 1 item (Box 21)
    "Princeton University 334 Campus Privilege." Letter enclosed. From letter: "Presumably, the Department of Grounds and Buildings issued these passes to vendors coming onto campus in years past."
  - Class of 1914 pin, 1 item (Box 2)
    Class of 1914. Orange pin with black lettering. "'14."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1634
  - Class of 1914 pin, 1916; 1 item (Box 2)
    Gold medal with Princeton Shield attached to orange and black ribbon. "E.W. Puttkammer 1914." "Member of Reception Committee 1916." "Western Assocation of Princeton Clubs."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1635
  - Reunion pin, 1956-06-09; 1 item (Box 2)
    Orange pin with black lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1956."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1637
  - Reunion pin, 1958-06-14; 1 item (Box 2)
    Orange pin with black lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1958."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1638
  - Reunion pin, 1959-06-13; 1 item (Box 2)
    Off-white pin with orange edges and black lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1959."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1639
  - Reunion pin, 1960-06-11; 1 item (Box 2)
    Orange pin with black lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1960."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1643
  - Reunion pin, 1961-06-10; 1 item (Box 2)
    White pin with orange edges and black lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1961."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1644
  - Class of 1914 55th reunion pin, 1969; 1 item (Box 2)
    Orange pin with black lettering. Class of 1914. "1914-1969, Princeton University."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1645
  - Whitman College dedication pin, 2007-09-27; 1 item (Box 2)
    Whitman College Dedication pin.
    Item 1646
  - Whitman College dedication pin, 2007; 1 item (Box 2)
    Whitman College dedication pin. "Murley-Pivirotto Family Tower."
    Item 1647
  - Whitman College dedication pin, 2007; 1 item (Box 2)
    Whitman College dedication pin. "1981 Hall."
    Item 1648
  - Whitman College dedication pin, 2007; 1 item (Box 2)
    Whitman College dedication pin. "Fisher Hall."
    Item 1649
  - Whitman College dedication pin, 2007; 1 item (Box 2)
    Whitman College dedication pin. "Hargadon Hall."
    Item 1650
  - Whitman College dedication pin, 2007; 1 item (Box 2)
    Whitman College dedication pin. "Lauritzen Hall."
    Item 1651
  - Whitman College dedication pin, 2007; 1 item (Box 2)
    Whitman College dedication pin. "South Baker Hall."
    Item 1652
  - Whitman College dedication pin, 2007; 1 item (Box 2)
    Whitman College dedication pin. "Community Hall."
    Item 1653
  - Class of 2004 pin, circa 2004; 1 item (Box 2)
    Class of 2004. White button with tiger and "'04."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1655
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 2)
    AR.2005.004, Item 1656
  - Princeton Employee pin, undated; 1 item (Box 2)
    Orange pin with university seal and motto. "Princeton University Employee."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1659
  - Silver Princeton pennant charm, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
    #1689
  - Pin with Princeton shield, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
    #1690
  - Reunion pin, 1941-06-14; 1 item (Box 4)
    White pin with blue edge and red lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1941"
    AR.2007.040, Item 1608
  - Reunion pin, 1946-06-22; 1 item (Box 4)
    White pin with orange edges and black lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1946."
    AR.2007.040, Item 1609
  - Class of 1911 reunion pin, 1916; 1 item (Box 4)
    Black pin with orange lettering. "1911" "Fifth Reunion"
    AR.2005.035, Item 1620
  - 1911 reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 4)
    Orange pin with black lettering. "1911"
    AR.2005.035, Item 1621
  - Reunion pin, 1931-06-18; 1 item (Box 4)
    White pin with orange lettering. "Alumni Parade 1931."
    AR.2005.035, Item 1622
  - Reunion pin, 1936-06-13; 1 item (Box 4)
    Brown pin with white lettering. "Alumni Parade 1936."
    AR.2005.035, Item 1623
  - Reunion pin, 1941-06-14; 1 item (Box 4)
    White button with blue edges and red lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1941."
    AR.2005.035, Item 1624
  - Reunion pin, 1951; 1 item (Box 4)
    Black pin with orange lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1951."
    AR.2005.035, Item 1625
  - Reunion pin, 1951-06-09; 1 item (Box 4)
    AR.2005.035, Item 1626
  - Pin with football, undated; 1 item (Box 4)
    Orange and black pin with gold football ornament attached.
    AR.2007.063, Item 1628
  - Name tag, undated; 1 item (Box 4)
    White name tag with black lettering and tiger with University seal.
    AR.2003.061, Item 1633
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 4)
    White pin with black edges and orange lettering. "E.W. Putkammer."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1636
  - Reunion pin, 1959; 1 item (Box 4)
    Orange pin with black lettering. Class of 1914. 45th Reunion. "Ernst W. Puttkammer."
    AR.4007.016, Item 1640
  - Reunion pin, 1959; 1 item (Box 4)
    Orange pin with black lettering. Class of 1914. 45th Reunion. "Mrs. Putt."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1641
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 4)
    Orange pin with black lettering. Class of 1914. "Wilfred Puttkammer."
    AR.2007.016, Item 1642
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 4)
    Gold ROTC pin in the shape of the American seal (eagle with a shield, holding olive branch and arrows).
    AR.2004.097, Item 1654
  - 10th Reunion pin, 1984; 1 item (Box 5)
    Class of 1974. Orange.
    AR.2007.004, Item 1606
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 5)
    Class of 1916. Orange with black lettering. "Jake Wortendyke."
    AR.2007.076, Item 1607
  - Reunion pin, 1957 June 15; 1 item (Box 5)
    Black pin with orange lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1957."
    AR.2007.040, Item 1610
  - Pin, 1896; 1 item (Box 5)
    Yellow pin with University seal. "Republican Club of Princeton University" and pictures of William McKinley and Teddy Roosevelt
    AR.2004.097, Item 1611
  - 50th Reunion pin, 1995; 1 item (Box 5)
    Class of 1945. Off-white pin with University Seal. "Stan Root"
    AR.2004.097, Item 1612
  - 55th Reunion pin, 2000; 1 item (Box 5)
    Class of 1945. White button with tiger in hammock. "Stan Root" "'43, '44, '46, '47."
    AR.2004.097, Item 1613
  - Class pin, undated; 1 item (Box 5)
    Class of 2005. Senior class button. White and black.
    AR.5007.016, Item 1616
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 5)
    Orange ribbon with button attached. Class of 1932. Picture of tiger on button.
    AR.2005.042, Item 1619
  - Reunion pin, 1992; 1 item (Box 6)
    Class of 1942. 50th reunion. Black pin with orange edge. "Louise Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1865
  - Reunion pin, 1982; 1 item (Box 6)
    Class of 1942. 40th reunion. White pin. "Louise Bingham '42."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1866
  - Reunion pin, 1971; 1 item (Box 6)
    Class of 1941. 30th reunion. Orange pin with white stripes. "Jim Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1867
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 6)
    Class of 1942. Orange pin with gothic style lettering "Friar" "Louise Bingham '42."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1868
  - Reunion pin, 1962; 1 item (Box 6)
    Class of 1942. 20th reunion. "Louise Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1869
  - Reunion pin, 1990; 1 item (Box 6)
    1990 Reunion pin. Orange pin with white stripes. "Old Combine 38 39 40 41 42." "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1871
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 6)
    Orange pin with black lettering. "Princeton University National Alumni Ass'n" "Bing."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1873
  - Reunion pin, 2003; 1 item (Box 6)
    Class of 1943. 60th reunion. "Art Oschwald" "38 39 40 41 42 44."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1874
  - Reunion pin, 1991; 1 item (Box 6)
    1991 Reunions pin. Black pin with orange stripe. "Art Oschwald."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1876
  - Reunion pin, 1987; 1 item (Box 7)
    Class of 1942. 45th reunion. Orange pin with black lettering "Original Combine" "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1855
  - Reunion pin, 1995 May 25-28; 1 item (Box 7)
    Class of 1940. 45th reunion. Orange pin with black lettering. "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1856
  - Reunion pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 7)
    Class of 1941. 55th reunion. Orange pin with Nassau Hall logo and black lettering "Bill Bingham '42."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1857
  - Reunion pin, 2001; 1 item (Box 7)
    Class of 1941. 60th reunion. Orange pin with black lettering "Bill Bingham '42."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1859
  - Reunion pin, 1978; 1 item (Box 7)
    1978 reunions pin. "Old Original Combine '38 '39 '40 '41 '42 '43." "Bill Bingham"
    AR.2009.112, Item 1860
  - Reunion pin, 1989; 1 item (Box 7)
    Oval-shaped pin from 1989 reunions. "Bill Bingham" "1938-1939-1940-1941-1942."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1861
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 7)
    Oval-shaped pin. Orange pin with black lettering. "1938-1939-1940-1941-1942-1943" "Bing."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1862
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 7)
    Class of 1942. Oval-shaped pin. Orange with black lettering. "Bing"
    AR.2009.112, Item 1863
  - Reunion pin, 1974; 1 item (Box 7)
    1974 Reunions pin. Oval-shaped and orange with black lettering. "Old Original Combine '38-'40-'41-'42-'43." "Bing"
    AR.2009.112, Item 1864
  - Reunion pin, 1959; 1 item (Box 7)
    Class of 1942. 1959 Reunions. Orange oval-shaped pin. "Bill Bingham" "1938-1940-1941-1942-1943."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1870
  - Reunion pin, 1958; 1 item (Box 7)
    1958 Reunions pin. Orange oval-shaped pin "1939-1940-1941-1942." "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1872
  - Reunion pin, 1969; 1 item (Box 7)
    1969 Reunions pin. Orange oval-shaped pin. "Louise Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1875
  - Reunion pin, 2006; 1 item (Box 8)
    Class of 1941. 65th reunion. White pin with tiger holding flag. "Old Original Combine" "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1847
  - Reunion pin, 1984; 1 item (Box 8)
    Class of 1939. 45th reunion. Orange pin with black lettering "Original Combine" "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1848
  - Reunion pin, 1994; 1 item (Box 8)
    Class of 1944. 50th reunion. Orange pin with black lettering "Bill Bingham '42."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1849
  - Reunion pin, 1986; 1 item (Box 8)
    Class of 1941. 45th reunion. Orange pin with black lettering "Original Combine" "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1850
  - Reunion pin, 2004; 1 item (Box 8)
    Class of 1944. 60th reunion. Orange pin with black lettering "Bill Bingham '42."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1851
  - Reunion pin, 2008; 1 item (Box 8)
    White pin with black lettering "Reunions Old Guard" "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1852
  - Reunion pin, 1981; 1 item (Box 8)
    Class of 1941. 40th reunion. White pin with black lettering "Bing."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1853
  - Reunion pin, 1998; 1 item (Box 8)
    Class of 1938. Class of 1943. 55th and 60th reunion. Orange pin with black lettering "The Old Original Combine" "Bill 'Bing' Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1854
  - Reunion pin, 1985; 1 item (Box 8)
    Class of 1940. 45th reunion. Orange pin with white stripe. "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1858
  - Reunion pin, 1993; 1 item (Box 9)
    Class of 1942. 51st reunion. "'39-'45" "Bill Bingham '42."
    AR.2009.112, Item
  - Reunion pin, 1988; 1 item (Box 9)
    Class of 1943. 45th reunion. "Bill Bingham '42."
  - Reunion pin, 2007; 1 item (Box 9)
    Class of 1942. 65th reunion. White pin with orange edge. "Sure Alive at Sixty Five!" "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1843
  - Reunion pin, 2002; 1 item (Box 9)
    Class of 1942. 60th reunion. White pin. "Swing to the 60th" "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1844
  - Reunion pin, 1980; 1 item (Box 9)
    Class of 1940. 40th reunion. Orange pin with black lettering "Original Combine APGA" "Bill Bingham."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1845
  - Reunion pin, 2005; 1 item (Box 9)
    Class of 1940. Class of 1945. 60th and 65th reunion. "Bill Bingham '42."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1846
  - Reunion pin, 1989; 1 item (Box 10)
    1989 Reunions pin. Black pin with orange stripe.
    AR.2009.112, Item 1877
  - Pin, 2000 Oct. 20; 1 item (Box 10)
    Anniversary Campaign Celebration pin. Orange pin with black and white lettering "Rejoice!"
    AR.2009.112, Item 1881
  - Pin, 2010; 1 item (Box 10)
    Wilson College 50th Anniversary Celebration pin. Red pin with picture of Woodrow Wilson.
    AR.2010.094, Item 1886
  - Reunion pin, 2010; 1 item (Box 10)
    Class of 1995. 15th reunion. White pin with orange edge and black lettering "95's Fifteenth Squadron" "Top Tiger" and tiger pilot logo.
    AR.2010.094, Item 1887
  - Reunion pin, 2010; 1 item (Box 10)
    Class of 1955. 55th reunion. White pin with tiger blowing horn logo.
    AR.2010.094, Item 1888
  - Reunion pin, 2010; 1 item (Box 10)
    Class of 2010. Reunion pin. White pin with X logo and Princeton shield.
    AR.2010.094, Item 1889
  - Reunion pin, 2010; 1 item (Box 10)
    Class of 2005. 5th reunion. White pin with superhero tiger logo. "Truth, Justic and the '05 Way."
    AR.2010.094, Item 1891
  - Reunion pin, 2010; 1 item (Box 10)
    Class of 1945. 65th reunion. White pin with tiger lying on hammock logo.
    AR.2010.094, Item 1892
  - Reunion pin, 2010; 1 item (Box 10)
    Class of 2000. 10th reunion. Orange pin with with palm tree. "'00 hangs 10."
    AR.2010.094, Item 1893
  - Reunion pin, 1954-06-12; 1 item (Box 11)
    1954 Reunions. "Alumni P-Rade 1954." Orange pin with black lettering.
    AR.2009.112, Item 1878
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 11)
    Orange pin with black lettering "Beat Yale."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1880
  - Pin, 2001; 1 item (Box 11)
    175th Anniversary pin. White pin with Princeton shield. "Princeton University Alumni Association" "1826-2001."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1882
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 11)
    White pin with red lettering "I am a Wayne Public Library Donor."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1883
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 11)
    White pin with grey "LMV" logo. "Not for Women Only."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1884
  - Reunion pin, 2010; 1 item (Box 11)
    Class of 2010. Orange pin with tiger logo. "Year of the Tiger."
    AR.2010.094, Item 1890
  - Pin with locomotive cheer, undated; 1 item (Box 11)
    Black, rectangular pin with the locomotive cheer "Hip, Hip, Rah, Rah, Rah, Tiger, Tiger"
    AR.2010.134, Item 1903
  - "Un-curl" pin, undated; 1 item (Box 11)
    Round orange pin with black letters that say "Un-curl"
    AR.2010.134, Item 1904
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 12)
    Princeton Tower Club 100th anniversary pin.
    AR.2005.048, Item 1614
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 12)
    Princeton Shield pin. Orange and black
    AR.2004.097, Item 1615
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 12)
    Class of 1970. Locust with Princeton Shield on its back.
    AR.2006.005, Item 1617
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 12)
    Gold pin with a lion and key. "Princeton Key and Seal Club." Engraved on back "P.C.W. '19"
    AR.2004.110, Item 1618
  - Pin, circa 2008; 1 item (Box 12)
    Gold pin. Princeton Shield.
    Item 1629
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 12)
    Class of 1896. Gold and black pin with star patterns.
    AR.2006.044, Item 1630
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 12)
    Black and orange pin. Class of 1896.
    AR.2006.044, Item 1631
  - Lapel pin, undated; 1 item (Box 12)
    Princeton Balloon Club pin.
    Item 1632
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 12)
    Black and orange "P" logo.
    Item 1657
  - Pin, circa 1922; 1 item (Box 12)
    Pennant shaped metal pin, half black and half orange, with lettering that says "Princeton"
    AR.2011.092, Item 1901
  - Pin, circa 1922; 1 item (Box 12)
    Small, round, scalloped-edged metal pin has Princeton shield
    AR.2011.092, Item 1902
  - Anniversary Campaign pin, undated; 1 item (Box 12)
    Black and white shield, with "ONE" under it.
  - Button, undated; 1 item (Box 18)
    Orange button with black lettering. "Princeton."
    AR.2005.035, Item 1627
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 18)
    Silver square pin. "Princeton University," "154," "Campus Privilege."
    Item 1658
  - Button, 1964; 1 item (Box 18)
    Orange button with black lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1964."
  - Reunion pin, 1997; 1 item (Box 18)
    Class of 1942. 55th reunion. White pin with orange edge. "Louise Bingham" "38 39 40 41 43."
    AR.2009.112, Item 1885
  - Silver bookmark with Princeton shield, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
    #1691
  - 40th reunion ribbon, 1900; 1 item (Box 26)
    Yellow or faded orange with gold fringes, "Princeton University," "40th Anniversary June 1900" in silver; black band across the ribbon, "Class of '60" in gold; gold pin.
    EX4109
  - 50th reunion ribbon, 1910; 1 item (Box 26)
    Yellow or faded orange, with "Princeton Class of 1860 Jubilee June 1910" in black; gold pin.
  - Reunion ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "'73" in black.
  - Reunion ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "74" in black; black knotted ribbon.
  - 11th reunion ribbon, 1909; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with drawing of two tigers holding an olive branch together, "Eleventh Annual Reunion Class of '98" in black.
  - Ribbon, 1906; 1 item (Box 26)
    Yellow, with the metal engraving of "Asst Clerk of Course" attached to black band across the ribbon; "Annual Indoor H'D'CP Games Gymnasium Princeton, N.J. March 21, 1906" in gold; gold pin.
  - Ribbon, 1906; 1 item (Box 26)
    Yellow, with the metal engraving of "Asst Clerk of Course" attached to black band across the ribbon; "Caledonian Games Princeton, N.J. March 21, 1906" in gold; gold pin.
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    White button with "P. U." in gold attached; metal engraving of "Guest" attached.
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, drawing of a tiger, "Princeton" in black.
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, flag-shaped, "Princeton" in black; gold staff-pin.
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with a seal, "Compliments of Eugene P. Peyser Men's Outfitter," "Princeton" in black.
  - 55th reunion ribbon, 1915; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "Princeton '60 June 12, 1915" in black; gold pin.
  - Reunion ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "Princeton '60" in black.
  - 25th reunion ribbon, 1903; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "Twenty Fifth 78 Reunion" in black; black bow.
  - Reunion ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "Class of '78" in black.
  - Reunion ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "'78" in black; black bow.
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Yellow or faded orange, with "'86," "Guest" in black.
  - Reunion ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "'87" in black; black bow.
  - 35th reunion ribbon, 1922; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "'87 June 1922" in black; orange pin gold-framed and engraved "35 Years After."
  - 10th reunion ribbon, 1898; 1 item (Box 26)
    Black and round with orange ruffles, "88" in gold; attached to orange and black ribbons, "Decennial" in black.
  - Reunion ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "'88" in black; black bow.
  - 10th reunion ribbon, 1899; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "Decennial '89 Reunion" in black; engraved bronze pin.
  - 30th reunion ribbon, 1919; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "'89 Thirtieth Reunion" in black.
  - Reunion ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "'92" in black; black knotted ribbon.
  - 5th reunion ribbon, 1898; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "'93 Quinquennial" in black; black knotted ribbon.
  - 17th reunion ribbon, 1911; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "Seventeenth '94 Annual" in black; gold-framed pin with "Princeton" in orange on black.
  - 13th reunion ribbon, 1911; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with drawing of two tigers holding an olive branch together, "Thirteenth Annual Reunion Class of '98" in black.
  - 14th reunion ribbon, 1912; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with drawing of two tigers holding an olive branch together, "Fourteenth Annual Reunion Class of '98" in black.
  - 60th reunion ribbon, 1961; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "Princeton 1901 Sixtieth Reunion June 10, 1961" in black.
  - Ribbon, 1915; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, "Princeton University Commencement Committee June, 1915" in black; gold pin.
  - Ribbon, 1916; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, "Princeton University Commencement Committee June, 1916" in black; gold pin.
  - Reunion ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "'68" in black.
  - Reunion ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "'68" in black; black knotted ribbon.
  - 45th reunion ribbon, 1915; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "Class of 70 45th Reunion 1915" in black.
  - 50th reunion ribbon, 1920; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, with "Class of 70 50th Reunion 1920" in black.
  - 30th reunion ribbon, 1905; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, "Class of 75 30th Reunion" in black.
  - Sesquicentennial ribbon, 1896; 1 item (Box 26)
    Black over orange, gold tassel; "Princeton Sesquicentennial Celebration 1896" in gold; "Class of '70" in black.
  - Sesquicentennial ribbon, 1896; 1 item (Box 26)
    Black over orange, gold tassel; "Princeton Sesquicentennial Celebration 1896" in gold; "Class of '73" in black.